Records of the Taller Martín Pescador Press, Juan Pascoe, Printer 1971-2014
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Taller Martín Pescador, in Mexico, 1975-ongoing; Series IV
  - Business card. Heriberto Vargas Jacob, Abogado. Logo top left, 2006-2007 (Box 2, Folder 5, Item 330b)
  - Marriage announcement for Ana Teresa y Prisciliano, 2010-ongoing (Box 2, Folder 6, Item 404)
  - Gilberto Gutiérrez y Tomás Segovia. Controversia Decimera, 2010-ongoing (Box 2, Folder 6, Item 406)
  - Business card. Crispin Fonseca Farias, Veracruz, 2010-ongoing (Box 2, Folder 6, Item 408)
  - Printing plate. Iván Fernández hizo esta jarana segunda para…, 2010-ongoing (Box 2, Folder 6, Item 409)
  - Linocut with ornament. Taller de Juan Pablos, Artemio Rodríguez, 2010-ongoing (Box 2, Folder 6, Item 410)
  - Bestario, Abecedario Ilustrado, 2010-ongoing (Box 2, Folder 6, Item 411)
  - Suhad Helú de Harp death announcement. Color photograph, 2010-ongoing (Box 2, Folder 6, Item 412)
  - Printing plate. Jesús Ramírez fabric esta jarana para…, 2010-ongoing (Box 2, Folder 6, Item 413)
  - Décima, Tomás Segovia. Para Agradecer la Controversia…, 2010-ongoing (Box 2, Folder 6, Item 414)
  - 65th wedding anniversary, Dorothy Pascoe Pierce y Juan Pascoe Strozzi, 2010-ongoing (Box 2, Folder 6, Item 416)
  - Printing plate. Año de 2010 Octavio Vega Hernández…, 2010-ongoing (Box 2, Folder 6, Item 417)
  - Printing plate. Iván Fernández hizo esta jarana para Valeria…, 2010-ongoing (Box 2, Folder 6, Item 418)
  - Espinosa Nova. Excelsa familia tipográfica inspirada en…, 2010-ongoing (Box 2, Folder 6, Item 420)
  - Herbazal. Grabados del taller de Artemio Rodríguez, 2010-ongoing (Box 2, Folder 6, Item 421)
  - Los grabados en la obra de Juan Pablos, María Isabel Grañén…, 2010-ongoing (Box 2, Folder 6, Item 422)
  - Inventing Italics, John Ridland, 2010-ongoing (Box 2, Folder 6, Item 427)
  - Mi primera comunión. Méndez, Palacios, Grañén, Moreno…, 2010-ongoing (Box 2, Folder 6, Item 428)
  - Book spine. Los grabados en la obra de Juan Pablos, 2010-ongoing (Box 2, Folder 6, Item 429)
  - Son Pascoe. Música y letra de Gabriel Aguilar Ramírez…, 2010-ongoing (Box 2, Folder 6, Item 430)
  - 1539-2011, 427 aniversario de la imprenta en México…, 2010-ongoing (Box 2, Folder 6, Item 433)
  - Un día, hace un año, entré al hospital –que es vacío, donde…, 2010-ongoing (Box 2, Folder 6, Item 434)
  - Card. Alfredo Harp Helú, María Isabel Grañén Porrúa…, 2010-ongoing (Box 2, Folder 6, Item 435)
  - Emiliano Gutiérrez Farías. Cumple su primer año de vida…, 2010-ongoing (Box 2, Folder 6, Item 437)
  - Árbol Caído, Everado Rodriguez, 2010-ongoing (Box 2, Folder 6, Item 440)
  - Estampas religiosas impresas de las placas originales del…, 2010-ongoing (Box 2, Folder 6, Item 441)
  - Business card. Pascoe Associates L.L.C., undated (Box 2, Folder 7, Item [none])
  - Dionisio Pascoe. Cherátaro, Obra Plástica, undated (Box 2, Folder 7, Item [none])
  - Taller Martín Pescador, Ediciones limitadas de poesia…, undated (Box 2, Folder 7, Item 47)
  - Instrument labels, possibly 1976-1978 (Box 2, Folder 7, Item 49)
  - Dos Décimas de Cuartela Obligada. Black and red text, undated (Box 2, Folder 7, Item 93)
  - Card. Illustrated landscape on card cover. No interior writing, undated (Box 2, Folder 7, Item 119a)
  - El dia. Cada mañana el niño… (2 copies), undated (Box 2, Folder 7, Item 137)
  - Pro Svsci-pienda… card, undated (Box 2, Folder 7, Item 149)
  - Pro Svsci-pienda… single cover page, undated (Box 2, Folder 7, Item 149a)
  - Photocopy. Santiago Pasco, mi bisabuelo…, undated (Box 2, Folder 7, Item 160)
  - Impreso para los amigos del Grupo Mono Blanco…, undated (Box 2, Folder 7, Item 196)
  - Book spine. A poem by Charles Tomlinson and Octavio Paz…, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 3, Folder 1, Item 63a)
  - Othón Téllez expone pintura, dibujo y grabado…, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 3, Folder 1, Item 64)
  - Hoja Suelta Numero Tres, Julio de MCMLXXX…, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 3, Folder 1, Item 73)
  - Cornelio Adrian Cesar. Impresor en la Nueva España…, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 3, Folder 1, Item 133b)
  - Paper copy of [133b] including mailing envelope, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 3, Folder 1, Item 133c)
  - Book spine. La obra de Enrico Martinez, Juan Pascoe, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 3, Folder 1, Item 155d)
  - Music record. Sones Jarochos con Arcadio Hidalgo y el Grupo…, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 3, Folder 2, Item [none])
  - Este es el ejemplar número, Mario Reyes poems, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 3, Folder 3, Item 90)
  - Dionisio Pascoe, Obra. Watercolor painting on announcement, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 3, Folder 4, Item 170)
  - Tepiton breve Inemachitiliz Zpianoyotl…, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 3, Folder 5, Item 177)
  - Declaraciones by Efraín Huerta, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 3, Folder 6, Item 224)
  - Gardenia y Dionisio, celebraron su enlace matrimonial…, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 3, Folder 7, Item 332)
  - Camino de Belén. Villanico de Navidad. Zéjel, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 3, Folder 7, Item 333)
  - Gilberto Gutiérrez esta guitarra para Jesús Ramírez Ortiz, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 3, Folder 7, Item 335)
  - 40th anniversary celebration of María Isabel Grañén…, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 3, Folder 7, Item 336)
  - Harry Duncan death announcement card, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 3, Folder 7, Item 338)
  - Death announcement for José Luis Martínez, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 3, Folder 7, Item 339)
  - Printing plate. Jesús Ramírez, Santa Rosa, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 3, Folder 7, Item 341)
  - Business card. Artemio Rodríguez, La Mano Press, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 3, Folder 7, Item 343)
  - Business card. Silvia Capistrán, La Mano Press, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 3, Folder 7, Item 344)
  - Gilberto Gutiérrez. Tres décimas para Lucy, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 3, Folder 7, Item 345)
  - Recorro tuy cuerpo y me asombro, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 3, Folder 7, Item 347)
  - Printing plate. Ex libris, Juan Pascoe, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 3, Folder 7, Item 349)
  - Homenaje al Bibliófilo MMVII, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 3, Folder 7, Item 350)
  - Printing plate. Ex libris Selva Hernandez L. Ccrossword pattern, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 3, Folder 7, Item 351)
  - Printing plate. Ex libris Selva Hernandez L. Pointed borders, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 3, Folder 7, Item 351b)
  - Printing plate. Feliz Cumpleaños Alfonso, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 3, Folder 7, Item 352)
  - Thesis defense announcement for Antoine Artuad, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 3, Folder 7, Item 354)
  - Tren de Noche, Raúl Eduardo González, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 3, Folder 7, Item 355)
  - Birthday invitation card. José Elián Urbina Hernández, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 3, Folder 7, Item 356)
  - Museo Textil de Oaxaca, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 3, Folder 7, Item 357)
  - Con tu luz, Juan Ramón Jiménez, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 3, Folder 7, Item 358)
  - Andrea, Gardenia Maldonado y dionisio Pascoe…, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 3, Folder 7, Item 359)
  - Ma. De la Luz Arévalo y Damian Maldonado participan…, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 3, Folder 8, Item 360)
  - Galería La Paloma, exhibition announcement postcard, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 3, Folder 8, Item 361)
  - Pascoe card announcement of Galería La Paloma exhibition, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 3, Folder 8, Item 361a)
  - Cumunicación visual Caminos de Tacámbaro…, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 3, Folder 8, Item 362)
  - Class graduation announcement. Escuela Secundaria Técnica 125, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 3, Folder 8, Item 363)
  - Dirección de Educación Pre-Escolar en el Estado de Michoacán, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 3, Folder 8, Item 364)
  - Monumental, Artemio Rodríguez un grabado Monumental y…, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 3, Folder 8, Item 365)
  - Despedida, Alejandro Aura, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 3, Folder 8, Item 367)
  - Illustration of Madonna figure, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 3, Folder 8, Item 369)
  - Illustration of printing press, signed by Artemio Rodríguez, 2008; Oversized materials. (Box 3, Folder 8, Item 370)
  - Book spine. Un Lustro, Adabi, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 3, Folder 8, Item 371)
  - Christian Urbina Hernandez cumple Seis Años el…, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 3, Folder 8, Item 372)
  - Disc. Juan Pascoe gave permission for library to publish…, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 3, Folder 8, Item 373)
  - Five views of The Graficomovil, by Artemio Rodríguez and…, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 3, Folder 8, Item 377)
  - Ximena Urbina Hernández nació el día de febrero…, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 3, Folder 8, Item 378)
  - Daniela Santillán y Román Zavala anuncian el nacimiento…, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 3, Folder 8, Item 379)
  - Inauguración, entre las 6 y las 9 pm del sábado…, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 3, Folder 9, Item 380)
  - Wedding invitation for Carla y Luciano. Envelope included, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 3, Folder 9, Item 381)
  - El Honorable Ayuntamiento de Tacámbaro invita al homenaje…, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 3, Folder 9, Item 383)
  - José Luis Aguilera Farías hizo esta guitarra en el Taller de…, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 3, Folder 9, Item 384)
  - Casa de los Pinos illustration, signed by Artemio Rodríguez, 2009; Oversized materials. (Box 3, Folder 9, Item 385)
  - Frida Sofia. Mis Papás José David Nájera Gómez y Josefina…, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 3, Folder 9, Item 388)
  - El rebaño, by José Rubén Romero, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 3, Folder 9, Item 390)
  - Printing plate. Ex-libris Victoria San Vicente, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 3, Folder 9, Item 391)
  - Printing plate. Ex-libris Jesús Ramírez Ortiz, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 3, Folder 9, Item 392)
  - Si se triza el azul, Ludwig Zeller, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 3, Folder 9, Item 393)
  - Gilberto Gutiérrez Silva. Décimas para Carmen Mulato, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 3, Folder 9, Item 394)
  - Virgen del Carmen, illustration. Signed by Artemio Rodríguez, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 3, Folder 9, Item 395)
  - Proyecto Libro Eterno. Encuadernaciones hechas a mano con…, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 3, Folder 9, Item 396)
  - María Isabel Harp Grañén. Te bendeciré y Serás una…, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 3, Folder 9, Item 397)
  - Santiago Harp Grañén. Dios es luz y en él no hay…, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 3, Folder 9, Item 398)
  - Stationary. Dionisio Pascoe, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 3, Folder 9, Item 399)
  - Business card. Jesús Ramirez Ortiz, Taller Martín Pescador, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 3, Folder 9, Item 400)
  - Historia de la imprenta en Oaxaca, 1685-1828, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 4, Folder 1, Item 190)
  - Dos Villancicos. Sor Juana Ines de la Cruz. (2 copies), undated; Oversized materials. (Box 4, Folder 1, Item 201)
  - Virgin of Guadalupe illustration, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 4, Folder 1, Item 206)
  - Canto a la primavera, Nezahualoyotzin Yxopancuic, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 4, Folder 1, Item 207)
  - San Agustin, tallado por Antonio de Espinosa en México…, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 4, Folder 1, Item 240)
  - Cover. Artisans ex libris del Mexicanos, siglo veinte, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 4, Folder 1, Item 241)
  - Tesis Universitario Mexicana. Impresa por Pedro Balli en 1584, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 4, Folder 1, Item [none])
  - Biblioteca Nacional de Mexico. Jose Luis Martinez, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 4, Folder 1, Item 303)
  - Dos textos Alberto Gonzalez de Leon en el primer año…, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 4, Folder 1, Item 311)
  - David Huerta. Premio Xavier Villaurrutia, dos poemas, 2006; Oversized materials. (Box 4, Folder 1, Item 324)
  - El Tajin, Efrain Huerta, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 4, Folder 1, Item 325)
  - Tomás Segovia, premio Juan Fulfo MMV. Ceremonial del Moroso…, undated; Oversized materials. (Box 4, Folder 1, Item [none])